Leo: Hello.
Barman: Good evening, sir, madam. What would you like to drink?
Leo: Do you have champagne?
Barman: Yes, sir.
Leo: Two glasses of champagne, please.
Barman: Here you are!
Leo: Cheers, Kim.
Kim: Cheers. To our new house.
Barman: You’re Americans, aren’t you?
Leo: Yes, that’s right. We’re from California.
Kim: But this afternoon we rented the big house near here.
Barman: Which house? The Travers family’s house?
Leo: Yes.
Barman: Oh.
Leo: Is something wrong?
Barman: Who showed you the house?
Kim: Barbara. The old lady who lived there before.
Barman: Ahh. Barbara. Old Mr Travers’ daughter.
Some people thought that she was the one that did it.
Kim: The one that did what? What happened?
Barman: Didn’t she tell you?
Kim: Tell us what?
Barman: About the murder.
Leo & Kim: Murder?
Barman: Yes, Mr Travers was murdered in that house in 1965…in his bed.
Kim: Oh, how horrible!
Barman: The man who killed Mr Travers was Barbara’s lover.
The family never lived there again.
They tried to sell the house, but nobody wanted to buy it.
Not after a murder. That’s why that house is always rented.
Barbara never married, of course.
Leo: Kim?
Kim: Yes?
Leo: Are you thinking what I’m thinking?
Kim: Yes – I don’t want to live in a house where somebody was murdered.
Come on. Let’s go.
Barman: Hey, hey, your champagne! You didn’t drink your champagne…
Ah, well.